Le Van Hop Software Engineer

Email: hople.dev@gmail.com

Phone: +84 916.797.006 - Skype: vanhop.av@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/hop-le-a90ba315b

SUMMARY

I'm a software engineer with 4 years of experience with JAVASCRIPT (which includes 1 year of experience at Mobile Developer with Flutter), with good knowledge of Object-Oriented, Design Patterns, Clean Code and Cloud Services.

Learning new languages and technologies is what I am passionate about. I'm con considered a team-player because I like to help others and tend to work well within the group. I can also do some mentoring tasks and do code reviews for other team members.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Programming Languages:
 - JavaScript, TypeScript
 - HTML, CSS
 - Dart, Python
- Frameworks/Platforms:
 - VueJS, ReactJS, Angular, ES6
 - Twitter Bootstrap, Web APIs
 - Flutter, ReactiveX

- Version Control, CI:
 - Git
- Foreign Languages:
 - English
- Soft Skills:
 - Time management
 - Business communication
 - Team work

- Other:
 - Good understanding of OOP methodologies, SOLID principles, design patterns
 - Good understanding of functional reactive programming (ERP)
 - Good knowledge Agile and Scrum development process
 - Good knowledge Cloud Services: AWS, Azure, Google Cloud Platform

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

AXON ACTIVE VN 05/2019 – present

Position: Software Engineer

EDUCASE

- Description: Educational management system
 Skill Set: HTML, CSS, Typescript, AngularJS
- Responsibilities:

Coding and fix the application's defect base on requirements using Typescript and AngularJS

AZWEBPLUS 01/2018 – 05/2019

Position: Software Engineer

SMART STORE

• **Project:** A startup project of AZWEBPLUS

• Skill Set: Adobe XD, HTML, CSS, Javascript, VueJS, Vuetify, Firebase, Flutter, Dart

• Responsibilities:

Design UI/UX using AdobeXD

Develop web app using Javascript, VueJS. Develop mobile app using Flutter, Dart Prepare documents and technical guide for developer joining in the middle of project Collaborate with team leader to define and improve the team's workflow

FANALUX

• **Project:** A management system of Fanalux nails spa

• Skill Set: HTML, CSS, JS, VueJS, ElectronJS, Dart, Flutter, AdobeXD

• Responsibilities:

Design UI/UX using AdobeXD

Develop web app using Javascript, VueJS

Develop mobile app using Flutter, Dart

Hiideas.vn

Project: A flooring ideas of Da Nang Science and Technology Information Center

• Skill Set: HTML, CSS, JS, VueJs

Responsibilities:

Coding and fix the application's defect base on requirements using VueJS

CNPT 03/2017 - 08/2017

Position: Junior Front End Developer

ABC Kids Garden System Management

- Project: A preschool management system with admin system and mobile app, delivering ABC Kid Garden services, resources, and information
- **Skill Set:** HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery
- Responsibilities:

Communicate with customers and teammates to clarify requirements. Design UI/UX and developed in HTML, CSS, JQuery

EDUCATION & TRAINING

• FPT Polytechnic Certification in Website Development (last 2017)